Roxane Connick Carlisle collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Photographs, Due to the small space in which to write on the slide mats, some of the information is unclear or difficult to understand. Carlisle's spelling of proper names of locations or ethnic groups reflect contemporary spelling. In these cases, the first instance is revised to reflec
  - Subseries 18: Botanical samples, structures, animals, people
    - Fisherman; White Nile, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1213 (Box 12)
    - David B. Carlisle as Arab; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1214 (Box 12)
    - David B. Carlisle as Arab; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1215 (Box 12)
    - David B. Carlisle as Arab; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1216 (Box 12)
    - David B. Carlisle as Arab; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1217 (Box 12)
    - David B. Carlisle as Arab; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1218 (Box 12)
    - David B. Carlisle as Arab; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1219 (Box 12)
    - Nuba Mountains; Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1220 (Box 12)
    - Nuba Mountains; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1221 (Box 12)
    - Nuba Mountains; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1222 (Box 12)
    - Nuba Mountains; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1223 (Box 12)
    - Nuba Mountains; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1224 (Box 12)
    - Nuba Mountains; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1225 (Box 12)
    - Nuba Mountains; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1226 (Box 12)
    - Boswellia; Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1227 (Box 12)
    - Boswellia papyrifera; Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1228 (Box 12)
    - Nuba village; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1229 (Box 12)
    - Nuba village; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1230 (Box 12)
    - Nuba village; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1231 (Box 12)
    - Nuba village; Kordofan, November 1966, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1232 (Box 12)
    - Mirri Bara; Nuba Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1233 (Box 12)
    - Acacia albida; Mirri, Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1234 (Box 12)
    - Acacia albida; Mirri, Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1235 (Box 12)
    - Male dancer Nuba; Mirri Bara, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1236 (Box 13)
    - Female dancer, Nuba, Mirri Bara, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1237 (Box 13)
    - Female singer, Nuba; Mirri Bara, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1238 (Box 13)
    - Nuba dancer; Mirri Bara, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1239 (Box 13)
    - Nuba flautist, Mirri Bara, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1240 (Box 13)
    - Nuba flautist, Mirri Bara, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1241 (Box 13)
    - Horn player; Mirri Bara; Dar Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1242 (Box 13)
    - Village dance; Mirri Bara; Dar Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1243 (Box 13)
    - Village dance; Mirri Bara; Dar Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1244 (Box 13)
    - Tribal dance; Mirri Bara; Dar Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1245 (Box 13)
    - Village dance; Mirri Bara; Dar Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1246 (Box 13)
    - Nuba women; Mirri Bara, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1247 (Box 13)
    - Keilak fishermen; Nuba, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1248 (Box 13)
    - Cotton flower; Kadugli, Nuba, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1249 (Box 13)
    - Cotton flower; Kadugli, Nuba, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1250 (Box 13)
    - Cotton flower; Kadugli, Nuba, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1251 (Box 13)
    - Cotton bolls; Kadugli, Nuba, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1252 (Box 13)
    - Cotton bolls; Kadugli, Nuba, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1253 (Box 13)
    - Diseased cotton; Kadugli, Nuba, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1254 (Box 13)
    - Dysdercus nymph on cotton; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1255 (Box 13)
    - Dysdercus nymph on cotton; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1256 (Box 13)
    - Cotton market; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1257 (Box 13)
    - Cotton market; Kadugli, Kordofan, February 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1258 (Box 13)
    - David B. Carlisle at Entebbe (airport), Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1259 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1260 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1261 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1262 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1263 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1264 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1265 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1266 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1267 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1268 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1269 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1270 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1271 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1272 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1273 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1274 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1275 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1276 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1277 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1278 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1279 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1280 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1281 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1282 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1283 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1284 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1285 (Box 13)
    - Murchison Falls; Victoria Nile, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1286 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1287 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1288 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1289 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1290 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1291 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1292 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Murchison Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1293 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Murchison Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1294 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Murchison Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1295 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1296 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1297 (Box 13)
    - Victoria Nile; Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1298 (Box 13)
    - Victoria and Albert Niles; Murchison Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1299 (Box 13)
    - Victoria and Albert Niles; Murchison, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1300 (Box 13)
    - Baboons; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1301 (Box 13)
    - Elephant; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1302 (Box 13)
    - Elephant; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1303 (Box 13)
    - Elephant; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1304 (Box 13)
    - Elephant; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1305 (Box 13)
    - Hippo; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1306 (Box 13)
    - Giraffe; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1307 (Box 13)
    - Giraffe; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1308 (Box 13)
    - Buffalo; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1309 (Box 13)
    - Hartebeest; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1310 (Box 13)
    - Reedbuck; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1311 (Box 13)
    - Reedbuck; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1312 (Box 13)
    - Waterbuck; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1313 (Box 13)
    - Waterbuck; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1314 (Box 13)
    - Waterbuck; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1315 (Box 13)
    - Kob; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1316 (Box 13)
    - Kob; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1317 (Box 13)
    - Kob; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1318 (Box 13)
    - Kob; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1319 (Box 13)
    - Warthog, Kob; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1320 (Box 13)
    - Spur-winged plover; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1321 (Box 13)
    - Nile monitors; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1322 (Box 13)
    - Crocodile; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1323 (Box 13)
    - Crocodile; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1324 (Box 13)
    - Crocodile; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1325 (Box 13)
    - Crocodile; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1326 (Box 13)
    - Crocodile; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1327 (Box 13)
    - Crocodile; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1328 (Box 13)
    - Crocodile; Murchison Falls National Park, Uganda, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1329 (Box 13)
    - Commiphora; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, plastic mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1330 (Box 13)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1331 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1332 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1333 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1334 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1335 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1336 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1337 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1338 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1339 (Box 14)
    - Longonot; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1340 (Box 14)
    - Baboons; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1341 (Box 14)
    - Baboons; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1342 (Box 14)
    - Baboon, impala; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1343 (Box 14)
    - Waterbuck; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1344 (Box 14)
    - Grant gazelle; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1345 (Box 14)
    - Grant gazelle; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1346 (Box 14)
    - Dung beetles; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1347 (Box 14)
    - Zebra; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1348 (Box 14)
    - Zebra; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1349 (Box 14)
    - Zebra; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1350 (Box 14)
    - Zebra; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1351 (Box 14)
    - Zebra; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1352 (Box 14)
    - Zebra; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1353 (Box 14)
    - Zebra foal; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1354 (Box 14)
    - Zebra, giraffe; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1355 (Box 14)
    - Zebra, giraffe; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1356 (Box 14)
    - Giraffe; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1357 (Box 14)
    - Hartebeest; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1358 (Box 14)
    - Hartebeest; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1359 (Box 14)
    - Hartebeest; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1360 (Box 14)
    - Hartebeest; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1361 (Box 14)
    - Hartebeest foals; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1362 (Box 14)
    - Bushpig; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1363 (Box 14)
    - Bushpig; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1364 (Box 14)
    - Bushpig; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1365 (Box 14)
    - Ostrich; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1366 (Box 14)
    - Ostrich; Nairobi, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1367 (Box 14)
    - Dung beetles; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1368 (Box 14)
    - Dung beetles; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1369 (Box 14)
    - Dung beetles; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1370 (Box 14)
    - Dung beetles; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1371 (Box 14)
    - Sultan Hamid; Kenya. Armyworm, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1372 (Box 14)
      This may be Sultan Hamud, a town in Kenya.
    - Sultan Hamid; Kenya. Armyworm, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1373 (Box 14)
    - Palaeolithic handaxes, Masailand; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1374 (Box 14)
    - Lake Magadi; Kenya, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1375 (Box 14)
    - Bush; S. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1376 (Box 14)
    - Coastal dunes; S. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1377 (Box 14)
    - Thorns; S. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1378 (Box 14)
    - Dunes; S. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1379 (Box 14)
    - Dunes/thorns; S. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1380 (Box 14)
    - Nuba Mountains villages, probably April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1381 (Box 14)
    - Merka; S. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1382 (Box 14)
    - Forestry Station; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1383 (Box 14)
      Several men and women appear in the image.
    - Escarpment; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1384 (Box 14)
    - High plateau; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1385 (Box 14)
    - Somali boy; S. Somalia, April 1967, 35 mm slide: color, plastic mount (broken); AFC 2012/008: PH1386 (Box 14)
    - Sand dunes; S. Somalia coast, April 1967, 35 mm slide: color, plastic mount (broken); AFC 2012/008: PH1387 (Box 14)
    - Dunes/thorns; S. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1388 (Box 14)
    - Vegetation; S. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1389 (Box 14)
    - Escarpment; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1390 (Box 14)
    - Escarpment; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1391 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia; escarpment, clouds, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1392 (Box 14)
    - Wadi, hills; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1393 (Box 14)
    - Hill road; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1394 (Box 14)
    - Escarpment; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1395 (Box 14)
    - Escarpment road; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1396 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia; Sheikh Pass, May 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1397 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia; Sheikh Pass, May 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1398 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia; Sheikh Pass, May 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1399 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia; Bulhar-Hargeisa Road, May 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1400 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia; Bulhar-Hargeisa Road, May 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1401 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia; New Road Bulhar, May 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1402 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia; escarpment, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1403 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia Wadi, May 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1404 (Box 14)
    - N. Somalia Wadi, May 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1405 (Box 14)
    - Somali sheep; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1406 (Box 14)
    - Somali sheep; N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1407 (Box 14)
    - Termitary, N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1408 (Box 14)
    - Termitary, N. Somalia, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1409 (Box 14)
    - Camel, Suaedia; N. Somali coast, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1410 (Box 14)
    - Camel, Suaedia; N. Somali coast, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1411 (Box 14)
    - Camel, Suaedia; N. Somali coast, April 1967, 1 slide: color, glass mount, 35 mm; AFC 2012/008: PH1412 (Box 14)